The reception is so damn horrible!
Interference?
What, "there may be?"
I have to know for sure!
Find out what's causing this!
We've got to look out. The princess is seeing red.
The HQ people just suck at their jobs.
They piss me off.
Now we can't contact Valmet and Tojo about meeting up in the next city.
And if that wasn't enough,
we've got these guys with us too now.
We have always treaded the borderland
I will adventure with you from here
Anyway, I don't know anymore what to say
We have always treaded the borderland
I will adventure with you from here
I can say maketaku wa nai
I can say I don't want to lose
demo kizu tsuketaku mo nai
but I don't want to get hurt either
te ni totte tasukerareteta
I got saved when the end was near
kitto modorenain da
so I guess there's no way out for me
demo sa
But you know...
I know
Don't watch now
kono koto ni te wo kase
Please help me with this
Don't watch now
hitozuki no me
You look like you would
Don't watch now
yasashisa no hate
Your eyes show kindness
We have always treaded the borderland
hirogeru ryoute keep balance
Spread your arms to keep balance
yori takaku toberu hou he
Always try to fly higher
mamoritai yo bokura no
I want to protect you
tsubasa no nai kono senaka ni
even if there are no wings on my back
seotta
I'll shoulder it
We are a killing team
They're the local border guards.
What should we do, Koko?
We've got to keep driving.
I'd like to see them stop a 20-ton truck with a KW—
Shit, is this a trap?
Stay in here, princess!
What the hell is going on?!
They seem to be fighting over the pipeline.
We're on a veritable battlefield.
Take a look and you'll see why reception was so bad.
The GSM cell phone base station,
the company station
and the microwave transmitter have all been blown sky high.
They can censor the information from this area now.
Not even satellites can reach this place.
No one knows there is a war here.
That's some insightful knowledge, Rem...
I guess.
Two large trucks and a lightly armed team.
They seem to be escorts.
There is a hysteric girl as well.
She's a buyer.
Don't shoot!
Chill, we're not enemies.
Though not friends either.
I am happy to see you here!
Ms Hekmatyar, you are surprisingly young indeed.
Nice to meet you, Major Polluck.
I'm truly sorry for the inconvenience my subordinates have caused you.
We have received the eight SAMs you brought.
Then, Major, I would like you to sign—
Don't be in such a hurry.
Have a seat, please.
When did all this start?
Barely 8 hours ago.
Lt. Col. Grant was supposed to accept the shipment.
He's still around.
Actual combat has a way of ruining careers.
Well, I suppose since the fighting started he hasn't been.
I shouldn't have asked.
This is bad.
Very bad!
The flames of war are raging here.
The commander will request an endless list of equipment.
I'll be dragged into this.
My signature.
By the way, I would like to place further orders for—
See, here it comes.
Oh, look!
Look who's there!
Long time no see, Koko!
Mildred! Lew!
Koko, where's Valmet?
She's on a mission.
But if you two are here, then—
Oh, my.
What a coincidence, Koko Hekmatyar.
Mr Currie, boss of the British CCAT.
Coincidence, my ass.
What do you want?
Who's this kid? A newbie?
This is like Christmas!
What did you buy from Mr Currie?
Stingers.
Used launchers, new missiles.
I brought them from Eastern Europe.
Isn't it wonderful?
We will once again see attack helicopters squashed like mosquitos.
Says you, the craven?
Cheaper, stronger, more.
That is what the battlefield wants.
That was all very interesting.
The contract is fulfilled. We should now—
Wait! I want to place further orders.
What?
A radar unit.
Our radar tower was destroyed in a bombing.
We need a field radar to replace it.
Too bad, I don't have access to such heavy equipment.
Neither do I.
But you do!
You're the daughter of the shipping magnate Floyd Hekmatyar.
You're a high-ranking representative of HCLI's weapons shipment branch for Europe and Africa,
Koko Hekmatyar.
Do you expect me to believe the little princess has no spare radar units sitting around?
Is he trying to push me into this?
No! No, no and no!
No!
What is she doing?
I need you here! All units!
Over my dead body, fuckers!
Lutz, stand down!
Let's put a stop to this.
We're not in a John Woo flick.
Major Polluck, your gentle face hides a hard man.
You've already won the information war.
Your men are killing all the civilians and journalists who escaped into the mountains, right?
Why would you go so far to hide a battle over a pipeline?
Are you trying to hold it for yourself?
Oh, please. Those are harsh words.
Don't they say soldiers are paid for killing?
If so, then my men are paid for a job well done.
Justice is with you as you let us prolong our wars.
I need your goods. Do it for justice.
Well, then. I expect the radar.
Do excuse me now.
And please, don't worry about the payment.
Looks like the storm has passed. Right?
My, my, the new commander is sure hard to deal with.
Not really. D'you want to shuffle home soon?
See you!
So what now, Koko?
It's not like we have many options.
We're getting out of here.
We'll pretend we accepted the contract.
We've got to rendezvous with Valmet and Tojo too.
According to my sources, these troops have hardly any money left.
It doesn't matter how persuasive he tries to be.
He's basically telling us he will pay us if he's victorious.
I, Koko Hekmatyar, would never do business on credit!
Hey, Tojo... I think we should've waited for Koko at the mountain pass.
We wouldn't have been able to help anyway. They're in deep now.
The sun is going down but they're still fighting.
They're nuts.
Just what's up with this battle? It's like a hornet's nest.
It certainly feels that way.
Let's go back to the pass in the morning.
Carefully.
Yeah...
We can finally charge our phones.
It's been a while since I slept under the open sky.
You'll be able to contact the HCLI HQ by phone as soon as you go over the pass.
This is one of few areas in Europe where even your precious Iridium phone is out of range.
Oh, so you knew I had one?
No signal, as you said.
Two of my top men will escort you.
They should be able to help you make it over the pass safely.
Leash for the dog, huh?
Take care, then.
Don't run away pretending you accepted my offer.
Fucking arms dealers.
It's been ten minutes and he's already insulting us?
All you do is pour oil into the fire. Into a pyre of men.
Is that beyond you, with your fancy university degree?
I'm just your average merchant.
I never went to any proper sort of school, not to mention university.
But I spent more time with my goods
than you did on your way to becoming one of his "top men."
Just seeing my goods in the hands of someone playing soldier like you
is as depressing as asking fish what flight is.
Shut up unless I ask for the way.
The fuck was that, kiddo?!
We've passed the summit.
This is one hell of a fog.
Jonah, I think we're in range now.
Want to give it a shot?
Call Tojo.
We have reception.
We do? Excellent!
Mi-24V, Hind E!
They are Russian Hinds!
Everyone take cover!
Get away from the trucks!
They're firing.
There must be mountain infantry in the area.
A Stinger...
It missed.
Who are you?
I'm the arms dealer working for Major Polluck.
Did another unit fire the stinger?
I can't tell a civilian!
They're all dead meat.
Pull back and get away from the Hinds.
Those are flying butchers.
Look at their sensor pods! That's an infrared camera.
They changed the standard Ladoga F night vision sensors
to an Eastern European third party make.
We're huge blobs on their screens.
That was close.
This bitch was smiling all along.
She's nuts.
Get lost, lucky girl.
I know the way.
Why aren't you trying to sell them weapons?
Jonah.
My guts are telling me this fight will be over in two days.
I'm not saying that either side will win.
The Russians can't fight on all fronts at the same time,
and the major has no money to see his plans through.
This dreary battle will turn into a low intensity conflict.
Neither can control the pipeline that just spits out money.
Of course, some of the merchants enjoy watching the endless struggle and supply them with weapons.
Frankly, they're the majority.
But the way I see it, this war has no more appeal when it comes to selling.
Are you going to trust your guts?
Yes. That's what kept us all alive until now.
Something wrong?
Die!
What are you doing, Mildred?!
They were pissing me off.
I don't give two shits how elite they are
if they can't keep their bloody mouths shut.
The leash he put on us may have been the only way to go over the pass!
You've ruined all my plans!
I can't believe this! You moron! You war nut!
Give me the map.
How short his fuse is! He's the boss for a reason.
What's taking you so long?
I'm confirming the locations for the retrieval of the goods.
Koko, what about those two?
Don't kill them. Do it quietly.
Tie them up!
Gag him too. He's an obnoxious idiot.
I was so worried, Valmet!
I was worried too!
Whoa, this feels great!
Okay, party full?
Let's get going!
My nose is bleeding.
Oh, it's just you, Lew.
Guys, the CCAT people are here.
They invited us in!
Actually, I, uh...
What a surprising meeting here!
Curious coincidence...
I thought you'd be back in England by now.
Long time no see.
Mildred.
I want to know more about you.
I really want to know how you live.
I want to put your combat skills to the test again.
I couldn't care less.
Boss!
Shut the hell up!
It's your fault we're in this mess!
Get a grip!
I can't!
Did you kill your escort?
No. Just bound and left them there.
That retarded girl cut off our own collar. Literally.
They might be after us.
Of course they are.
Can we send those two out to scout?
Valmet, I'm really sorry. Please do it.
No problem.
She asked me to. I have no choice.
Let's go.
Koko changed, didn't she?
Back in the day she was amazing.
Now she's just good.
She has always been and will be the best.
Let's do this!
Good! This is good!
This is so good! Why?
There's not a single scratch on you!
Shouldn't your eyepatch be a handicap in a knife fight?
I've never won, so I challenged you in the night!
Can you see in the dark or something, Valmet?!
I'm getting the impression that you've gotten slow.
It might feel nice to carry so many knives,
but they get in the way of your movements.
Even our greenhorn Jonah is calling you "the knife collection".
So he's called Jonah...
Why would you lead me to the knives you threw away?
Did you want to pull them out and reuse them,
claiming I let my guard down?
What's the problem?
If you let it go, consider it gone for good!
That's common sense!
Shit. Now she's lecturing me.
There's one team of ten: Koko Hekmatyar and her men.
There's another team of three: Currie and the CCAT people.
I prioritize... the first team.
Don't forget that while you're on the mission,
the Orin pass and the border road remain unguarded.
Understood, sir.
But it was the other team that killed our comrades.
I know that, damn it.
I've thought about it, you know.
You told me in the watch factory that you want to know more about me.
I don't think that's wise.
Why? I think you're great!
You were an elite soldier. They betrayed you and you lost it all.
But even then you kept training and stood back up! You're awesome!
You're exaggerating.
I really don't care about you, but I don't want you to go through the same as I did.
I've never had anything to lose!
I think people like us, the fighters, are hollow.
Totally empty.
Maybe after we first killed someone.
Maybe after we had our first weapon.
Protecting our family or country is just an excuse.
Even I know that.
I just think that if I were as good as you,
I'd have something to fill the void.
That's ridiculous.
Valmet!
This is it for today.
Next time I'll beat you bloody!
You can feel our pursuers, can't you? How far off?
500 meters!
Boss!
Why can't she be this sharp when it comes to other matters?
Prepare for battle!
We'll go ahead and clear a path.
We might be able to hold them off,
depending on their numbers.
You might not like it, but you'll owe me.
Your valiance is as astounding as ever, Hekmatyar.
Well, then.
Bye, Mildred.
There aren't many, but they have us surrounded.
Listen up, unit!
Drop your weapons!
What?!
Remove the magazines and fold the stock!
Listen to me, soldiers!
We are the larger team!
The team of three is inside!
Fucking vixen!
Shit! Shit!
Don't expect this to work every time.
Take the Orin pass and cross the border while we're busy.
Head north, lucky girl.
Make a beeline for it, guys!
Escape the killing field!
What's up, Jonah?
Nothing. It just feels weird.
First time I haven't fired a single bullet on a battlefield.
All right! Prepare to fire until your barrel starts glowing next time!
Do you get it now, Jonah?
You can't talk her into things.
She's an arms dealer.
Both of them? That's a problem.
Seems the smaller team is pretty good too.
Punishment? There is no need for that.
I can understand your choice and I will support you.
Taking responsibility is my job. No need to worry.
Now return to our post.
Once we set this up, the bombings stopped.
Their "goods" are either huge threats or just metal junk.
Koko Hekmatyar, the arms dealer.
What an unpredictable wench.
Took a day to die down?
Excuse me?
Never mind.
Have a nice trip.
Thank you.
We made it!
I'm so tired, boss!
Oh, you made it through?
hikari yo kotaeru mata tsumi
Light shines on my newest sin
sougon no ma ni yurameku ayamachi
and I tremble in the solemn shine
fujou shite iki wo tsuki
I resurface and draw a breath
tokasare majiru dake no tsugunai wo te ni shita
But my salvation faded all too soon
mujun haramu kono sekai no tou
This world, filled with contradictions
omoi tsukashiteru zakuro no me ni
reminds me of a bead of garnet
wataru kumo ne fushi wa mou nai
There is no rhythm in the passing of the clouds
suiheiki no tsuranuku kodou
just a chaotic ripple on the water
Musica Ex Machina